<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>List of posts on Learn Build &amp; Break!</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in List of posts on Learn Build &amp; Break!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>How I broke into Google Issue Tracker</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/2018/04/10/how-i-broke-into-google-issue-tracker/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/2018/04/10/how-i-broke-into-google-issue-tracker/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends,
Recently, I published an article where I explained a flaw in google groups functionality. When I submitted that vulnerability to Google I noticed that researchers can comment on the issue in issue tracker by replying to the email from buganizer system.
After submitting three N/A (won’t fix) report to Google, finally I managed to submit one valid report but unfortunately that was marked as duplicate. Thanks to Google security team, they are very responsive and allowed me to write about the vulnerability.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hey! Organisations don’t underestimate DMARC policy!</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/2018/04/03/hey-organisations-dont-underestimate-dmarc-policy/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/2018/04/03/hey-organisations-dont-underestimate-dmarc-policy/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends,
It has been a long time since I have written, of course I am lazy. I was desperate to find bugs in Google &amp;amp; Facebook ( at least one valid ) so I thought let’s start with Google services. We all know about Google Groups, it is a service that provides discussion groups for people sharing common interests. Google Groups have a nice feature to post on groups by sending emails.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Little experience in bugbounty hunting</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/2017/06/19/little-experience-in-bugbounty-hunting/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/2017/06/19/little-experience-in-bugbounty-hunting/</guid>
        <description>Hello friends, hope you are doing well. Yesterday, I had gone for LinuxChix india meetup. I found some people interested in magic the bugbounty hunters do in finding the security loopholes. So I am sharing some resources as well as my experience. Oh, let me introduce myself, My name is Abhishek Bundela, undergraduate from Shri Mata Vaishno Devi University. I do bugbounty for the feeling of excitement and of course, for the cash.</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
